<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Health Game</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--Database is currently hardcoded-->
    <string name="banana_meal">Breakfast, Snack</string>
    <string name="banana_type">Fruit</string>
    <string name="banana_description">
        I love bananas! Long thick-skinned edible fruit that is yellow when ripe.
        Bananas are delicious eaten with one\'s fingers after peeling off the skin.
        Depending on the type of banana unripe bananas are also cooked, fried or deep-fried a lot. Bananas are the
        basic food in many tropical countries.</string>
    <string name="fries_meal">Lunch, Dinner</string>
    <string name="fries_type">Appetizer, Side</string>
    <string name="fries_description">
        French fries primarily contain carbohydrates from the potato
        (mostly in the form of starch) and fat absorbed during the deep-frying process, as well as
        sodium depending upon the seasoning. They are made by frying, salting, and removing one of
        the healthiest parts of the potato: the skin, where many of the nutrients and fiber are found.
        Avoid eating too much! </string>
    <string name="burger_meal">Lunch, Dinner</string>
    <string name="burger_type">Entré</string>
    <string name="burger_description">
        Hamburger is a kind of sandwich consisting of grilled cutlets, served inside
        that cut round loaf. It is usually supplemented with various seasonings, for example, lettuce,
        ketchup and mayonnaise, slices of pickled cucumber, tomatoes or zucchini, raw or fried onions.
        The burger is the most common fast food in the United States. Burgers are great foods to eat occasionally,
        but they are generally considered unhealthy.
        </string>
    <string name="pizza_meal">Lunch, Dinner</string>
    <string name="pizza_type">Entré</string>
    <string name="pizza_description">
        Pizza is a flatbread generally topped with tomato sauce and cheese and baked in an oven.
        It is commonly topped with a selection of meats, vegetables and condiments. Who doesn't love pizza?
        </string>
    <string name="salad_meal">Lunch, Dinner</string>
    <string name="salad_type">Entré</string>
    <string name="salad_description">
        A salad is a healthy dish consisting of small pieces of food, which may be mixed with a sauce
        or salad dressing. They are typically served cold. Salads can incorporate a variety of foods
        including vegetables and fruits. They may not taste very good alone, but adding stuff like
        cheese, cooked meat, eggs, grains, nuts, and dressing greatly improves the flavoring of salad.
        </string>


    <string name="yogurt_meal">Snack</string>
    <string name="yogurt_type">Side</string>
    <string name="yogurt_description">
        Yogurt is made by adding a number of types of harmless bacteria to milk, causing it to ferment.
        This thickens it and gives it its characteristically tangy flavour. Cow\'s milk is the most common
        type used, but goat\'s, ewe\'s, sheep or buffalo\'s milk are also suitable. Most yogurt sold is \'live\',
        which means that it still contains live bacteria. Such organisms are thought to stimuate the gut\'s
        friendly bacteria and suppress harmful bacteria.
        </string>

    <string name="chickenNuggets_meal">Lunch, Dinner</string>
    <string name="chickenNuggets_type">Appitizer</string>
    <string name="chickenNuggets_description">
        Chicken nuggets are in fact typically made of the same meat that you see in the supermarket, that is, broiler meat.
        Chicken nuggets are excellent sources of protein, especially for growing kids, which are part of a healthy, balanced diet
        that includes plenty of fruits and vegetables. I love eating them with ketchup or sweet-n-sour sauce. Be careful of eating
        too much of them, though!
        </string>

    <string name="burrito_meal">Lunch, Dinner</string>
    <string name="burrito_type">Entre</string>
    <string name="burrito_description">
        Burritos are so yummy, holy crap. I love the chicken and beans and rice and avacados and cheese and everything inside them tastes so good wiht the
        tortilla. Its not that unhealthy except the tortilla itself. Moreover its important to understand how much SALT IS IN THE BURRITO
        SO DONT EAT TOO MUCH CHILDREN unless you wanna get high BP and die or something. But burritos are very yummy I want one right now.
        </string>

    <string name="lucky_charms_meal">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="lucky_charms_type">Entre</string>
    <string name="lucky_charms_description">
    I love eating breakfast for cereal. Cereal is made from processed grains and can be very healthy depending on the brand.
        It is eaten hot or cold, usually mixed with milk, yogurt, or fruit. Some companies promote their products for the health benefits
        from eating oat-based and high-fiber cereals. My personal favorites include Cheerios and Lucky Charms
    </string>


    <string name="oreo_meal">Breakfast, Lunch, Dinner</string>
    <string name="oreo_type">Entre</string>
    <string name="oreo_description">
    I love oreos. They taste so good with milk or even with water. Eat a few, not too many as they have no nutritional benefits, but make
        sure to keep eating in moderation because they are very tasty.
    </string>






</resources>
